Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/adwaithviju182 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

HTML5

GitHub

E-Commerce

Languages

Malayalam (Limited Working)
Hindi (Limited Working)
English (Full Professional)

Certifications

Basics in Python Programming
Front-End Web UI Frameworks and

Tools: Bootstrap 4

Learn To Build a Real Time Website Like StackOverflow- MERN Stack

Adwaith Viju Thaivalappil

Frontend developer

Thane, Maharashtra, India

Summary

Prolific, full stack web developer Prototyped new product features for companies. Decreased rework by

22 percent and costs by 15 percent. Consistently receive high user experience scores for all web

development projects, including a 40 percent increase for the companies i have worked with. Passionate about building world class web applications

Also Reach out if you want to talk about emerging tech, Creating a new software or about songs.

Experience

Diginspire

Jr.Frontend Developer September 2023 - Present (1 month) India

Code Alpha Web Developer July 2023 - August 2023 (2 months)

NullClass

Full-stack Developer January 2023 - January 2023 (1 month)

Assignments are as follows

Integrate a chatbot feature where users can ask their questions directly to the chatbot.

It should answer all programing related questions
Authenticate with OTP before asking questions

2. Create subscriptions using a payment gateway (like stripe, razorpay) to post questions in stackoverflow.

Testcase: Free Plan can post only 1 question a day, silver plan will be #100/month which can post 5 questions a day and gold plan can post unlimited questions and priced at #1000/month.

3. Create a social media community where people can share images, and videos and get likes and shares and also be able to add friends and remove friends.

Testcase: Users can share their programming experience here using text, photos, and videos which can be viewed by others. Users can search, like, unlike, remove, add their friends.

Currently working on completion of the projects.

5G Infotech Frontend Web Developer August 2022 - September 2022 (2 months) Thane, Maharashtra, India

It has been a good experience and seeking to learn more

Electronic Arts (EA)
Software Engineering virtual internship
July 2022 - July 2022 (1 month)

Suven Consultants and Technology Pvt.Ltd.
Javascript Development
June 2022 - July 2022 (2 months)
Learning something new everyday

TareZameen Foundation Fundraiser June 2021 - July 2021 (2 months) inda

Education

Helped raising funds

Pillai College of Engineering

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Engineering · (August 2020 - October 2024)

Vani Vidyalaya Junior and Higher Secondary School

HSC, Science · (May 2018 - January 2020)